so we can take this essential matrix and
we can extract slam is simultaneous
localization and mapping it's s so we're
getting there
we're getting to what we're still
working on feature extraction between
pairs of frames the first step of any
slam pipeline is sparse hose recovery
from the essential matrix oh man
get that confusing crap won't they just
show me a Python code that's the problem
with math they read it in such confusing
ways all math should just be written in
Python okay so do I feel any way about
Mozilla removing the world and I can
thread to buzz
[Music]
it's a music
maybe that's change it was might as my
as my tea here picked up and on its way
it was might as my as my tea here picked
up and on its way
I don't understand why if I set up to 1
I get assertion error - it's an
assertion are you code I wrote oh it's
this huh yeah cuz that's on pixel scale
save it no window so window hiding my
game display so I make a new window
inside you hiding image load I'm not
bleeding anything to the screen
now right time to search for points
after going close optimization put you
to match to the fright peed on why
[Music]
oh that's beautiful Oh beautiful oh we
can even make that bigger a picture is
where it's bending pixels on 600 pixels
that's a lot of pixels yeah Vulpix fine
lose the track well you saw what it did
like it just looks shitty
you
you see thorough check
oh yeah I'm sure I would learn a lot if
I went to school yeah bro there's
nothing to do itself driving this is
Chuck what people like
yeah I mean sir company and like don't
start a couple own you might VC funding
like just go do something and Nick
profit I mean if you can scam movies
these all better for you but I do love
nature problem why do you sleep at work
and you are rich because I don't
you
it is interesting that makes you think
oh yeah they all not hired by oculus
rift um LSD slim guy kick a bangle Raul
more whatever yeah
they all got acquired by oculus no these
things are kind of annoying diplomat
like if don't know a lot of stuff to
write a slim so here's the video that
we're gonna drive see this it's a video
of some guy driving on a road and the
idea is can we figure out how that cars
moving and make a map of the environment
that he's driving through at the same
time so there are open source programs
to do this but we are gonna try to code
our own how many people are watching
right now can I tell its total views not
use for this you're not trying to do
this for this just do this why do I get
up in the Malayan to the border no I
don't take free interns
you'll comment a video link with
something good somewhere well if you'd
asked me when I was younger that can
work works small different variable
stupid let's just not thread for now
did I get my wits and Heights mixed up
I'm gonna do that it's really easy to
tell
stupid no I don't get my what's
tonight's best out
alright time
Wow that's true
you don't like my troubling nested
for-loops crows
because map data frame has side effects
right think that's the same no no no no
no we're not playing we're not playing
my rap so let's go listen to the fuel of
that around whether that actually runs I
think as long as I write it that way
it's okay but I think my right the other
way it's broken because map data frame
has side effects right think that's the
same
no no no when I put okay big small I
don't even know how to
oh cool um I wonder if anyone's actually
gonna come to this this was an awful
long oh cool my wonder if anyone's
actually gonna come to this Oh
instead of creating you were here we're
gonna change this to be this 2d Oh
instead of creating viewer here we're
gonna change this to be this 2d test
event process
let's get to control one of these days I
should really like dive deep sounds like
I can do it as an initializer to STL 2x2
window bullshit
I hate Python 3 how do i do Python 3
integers divide integer division is it
like two slashes or some crap and two
solutions all right my default resume is
different cuz I like you as long as it
native resolution can you guys see so
what we're doing is we're live coding
slam so we're going to try to write a
simultaneous localization and mapping in
Python ball eat mice and when you make a
matter rather than you passed in why not
do anything we don't like to code so
annoying because
look at the top here
like this isn't this isn't started zero
zero
[Music]
and $10 get all great
see how you built this you know what
you
[Music]
Ek dark sky how do I activate subs yeah
and what was watching the map data
sourcing the maps - recently I think
that about FPGAs and GPUs is you're just
not yeah this is the exact same logic
they just call it transform for for the
effort same have that same function Oh
what is it different why is this
different why did I put two two there so
if I D plus ten is less than that sounds
good I hope you don't find it out
nothing good it's not inspiring fuck you
know this is fucking bullshit man I hate
inspiring shit
inspire people to do what just go do
things if you want to do things do
things you don't need to be inspired
okay enough this is fucking bullshit man
I hate inspiring shit inspire people to
do what just go do things if you want to
do things do things you don't need to be
inspired don't care what would I do with
money I can't buy a better laptop they
don't have one yet
can't buy faster internet I mean yeah
[Music]
this is right so that's X that's why
that's it did you laughs channel yeah
it's about living system pretty cool so
that means we want to reject the points
reject points
what's wrong with Python three is that
it has wasted billions of dollars of the
world's time like if you think about if
they didn't make the two terrible
decisions they made a pile of tree which
was to remove the the breath the
plantation in the print statement it
really doesn't make sense print is a
statement like assert or race it
shouldn't be used in production code you
should be using logging library if you
want to do something that resemble
spectrum also most strings are not
designed to be outputted to people so
strings should not be unicode they
should be bytes if be welcome back to
live coding slam part two
no no tomorrow we have twitch stream rap
oh cool my what everyone's actually
gonna come to this
it's okay hunter I don't watch twitch
enough to know got a USB see the USB a
host probably work yo I love this piece
man oh man look at look at that screen
it's just like torn to shreds in there
yeah like this was breaking our pie
but okay so you see like when the
essential matrix runs like it goes like
that my foes optimizing okay why isn't
the pose optimizer fixing that that's
what I don't understand
nice
do I have other bugs I have to
oh okay so it actually looks like that
it's not pure rotation
that's oh now it's working I don't know
hello
[Music]
you
a company like Microsoft or Apple I mean
they kind of just wanna like you don't
like sell you a product right like they
wanna sell you a product or a service
that's fine that's like the engine of
capitalism that's what makes capitalism
great but really I mean capitalism when
it's based on consent I mean that is
consent right when I go when I purchase
an iPhone axis is a consensual
transaction between me an apple when
Google you know tracks my cookie around
the internet and then like uses
psychology to figure out what's most
likely to get me to click on an ad it's
not so consensual anymore right
maybe my game display flip isn't correct
we're gonna have to like painters copy
pixels into a 2d array copy it right
into a new surface does look look I have
like I have to rotate it
but we're back and let's go cheer now to
be number one let's try this weekly top
Cheers
all right
it sounds alright let's go back to
coding slap my ass got Messam Pangolin
gone let's go let's write some shit oh
you know what sucks though we're gonna
try to thread no I hate threads and by a
thread I mean a process because this is
a Python just do from the beginning I we
gotta think
well so maybe we can make this less
stupid first oh but now we're back to
that okay now we're back to the problem
of this
comes from a lot of different places
right okay so we could make them how do
I differentiate that
okay so numeric differentiation yeah
here we go
I mean like how do you do this well okay
so that's not numeric so I mean like
what that effectively you can think
about what that is right it's it's a and
then you have to linearize it let's go
get some coffee
I'll be back maybe someone made warm
coffee and I'll be very happy
honestly no but seriously how many
people can fucking do that right like
that's the real shit like you all twitch
programmers should be trolled like that
if you can't write bubblesort in ten
seconds get off twitch that's supposed
to be rotation it's not this stuff is so
on each row what is a parameter and each
know each column is a parameter and each
row oh thank you thank you now danger 7
thank you for subscribing denied
streaming
everything you do is public and you
gotta be careful with what you click on
kind of pull it aside conferences where
Def Con used to be about you know let's
let's be hackers let's be elite let's be
hacker culture it's drifted away from
from hacker culture to anybody can use
our dwee knows to be a hacker okay
that's not where I'm showing up I think
there are still some my career CCC is
actually still pretty good maybe I'll go
this year you know what I mean you all I
don't know what I mean right know what
we're gonna have to write the CRC
bullshit anyway so let's just write it
now
so they're CRC is a lot more recessive
than this CR C dou C or C only has a
little dominant well this here C is
mostly done so it's PI more probably
easier to set up there's such nice cans
I really want to use the cab can't use
the cans books we only have three of
them that's the whole reason we're doing
this that's right
capitalism that's right we love
capitalism light buzz that would be a
fun thing to write as well maybe that's
what we'll do next this is this is a no
thing so we can always we can always
look up yeah yeah I've tried Loula chest
this isn't the point so the point of
these two extremes is so we can all
learn together and you know I had a kind
of unfair advantage with twitch slam
because I'd already written a slam
before a small slam and it didn't work
as well as twist slam but okay so you
wanna sounds just so you know I'll have
to find the search tree now if you guys
are familiar we can look up basic comp
computer I love rice guys
she's got green hurry
[Music]
yo one Wayne's got some fun I swear you
can't fuck it seems like you're not
expandable oh don't understand
that's right no real experiments man is
so loud so loud like I have a choice
between am I too hot or is it too loud
you know you just can't win in life
aren't going to this Thai place it
doesn't taste as good when it's
delivered iLike flasks
[Music]
that's all right don't really how they
wipe teepees does the internet used to
be cool
[Music]
which boy get miss boy getting numbers
don't add up on the flow that was ten
years ago
Drake named it named one of his songs
after the day his kid was conceived I
just like I have listened to this making
my life easy alright so the function I
can call from is here it's a fuse that's
fucking a work I can certainly call this
alright what JavaScript make up my life
easy
so the function I can call from is here
it's a fuse that's not gonna work I can
certainly call this alright what
JavaScript yeah look do you really want
to contribute to the world
really yeah
it's overrated you you want to have
skill and talent and then not contribute
because that's funny
that's funny in McCall's
raincoat this is the life families
hanging out today I bought nice clothes
I got heck up
oh god get screen size and that's a nice